I'm about to get these tickets to the shows.
Getting Beyonce tickets, getting Beyonce tickets, getting Beyonce tickets.
Let me do something else, alright.
Tickets to Lil Wayne.
Going to a drink show, going to a drink show.
Aubrey don't feel me now.
Nikki, do you love me?
Baby, tickets.
Can you get tickets for me?
Wow, this is, this is, this is rent money.
What's a show where black people are going to be like singing along, having a good time and dancing?
Name 18, Los Angeles at the Novo downtown LA.
That's not going to make me feel like I'm paying student moms.
A variety comedy game show for the culture.
Beautiful black people.
We never get to see a space where we're celebrating positive images.
That war.
What's about this here?
Is this the part where we got to be intelligent?
Yes.
They trying to shut blackness down, but baby, we going to be lifting it up.
Get your affordable tickets today at AmandaSeals.com.
It's going to be black people there singing and laughing and dancing.
It's exactly what you're looking for.
Smart, funny, and black.